The Scene view is where you will visually construct your game.
シーンビューによりゲームを視覚的に構築することが出来ます。
And this can be navigated by making use of the buttons above the view.
そして操作はビューの上にボタンを活用して行います。
These buttons correspond to the Q, W, E and R buttons on the keyboard.
これらのボタンはキーボード上の Q, W, E および R ボタンに相当します。
The first button, the Hand Tool, is purely for navigating.
最初のボタンである、ハンドツールは操作に特化しています。
With this tool selected drag with the left mouse button to pan,
このツールを使用して、まづす左ボタンクリック＆選択ドラッグでカメラを移動（Pan）して、
and with the right mouse button to look around First Person style.
右マウスボタンにより、一人称視点で見回すことが出来ます。
Hold the Alt key with this tool and left mouse button drag
Alt キーを押したまま、マウス左ボタンクリック＆ドラッグで
will let you orbit around the point you were looking at.
現在のピボットポイント周りでカメラを回転します。
Whilst Alt and right mouse button dragging will zoom the view.
Alt キーを押したままマウス右ボタンクリック＆ドラッグで、シーンビューをズームします。
With any object selected in the hierarchy
Hierarchy ビューで任意のオブジェクトを選択した状態で、
you can focus on the object either by double clicking the object's name
オブジェクトにフォーカスするには、オブジェクトの名前をダブルクリックするか、
or by pressing F with the mouse cursor over the Scene view.
シーンビューでマウスカーソルをおいたまま F キーを押します。
The remaining three buttons allow you adjust position,
残る三つのボタンにより位置の調整が出来て、
rotation and scale of objects.
オブジェクトの位置（Position)、回転（Rotation）、大きさ（Scale）を調整できます。
By dragging the corresponding axis handles
対応する軸ハンドルをドラッグすることで
you can move objects in X, Y or Z.
オブジェクトを X, Y, Z 方向に移動することが出来ます。
Likewise this also applies to moving in 3D
同じような方法として、 3D 空間で移動する場合に
by dragging from the centre,
中心からドラッグすることもできます。
although this is not necessarily recommended
3D 空間で操作する場合はこの方法を
for moving in 3D space.
推奨するわけではないので注意ください。
Likewise for rotating you can rotate in all three axes,
同様にして回転する場合に、3 つの軸すべてに対して各々回転させることが出来ます。
or you can just drag from within those,
または、各々の中でドラッグできます。
but again a lack of control will occur
ただし、注意すべき点として、
when trying to drag in all three axes at once.
3 つの軸すべてを同時にドラッグをすると操作の利便性は失われます。
And again with scaling
さらに同様にして拡大する場合
you can scale objects in all three individual axes
オブジェクトを 3 つの各々の軸で拡大することが出来ます。
or drag from the centre point in order to scale uniformly.
または、中心の点からドラッグすることで均一に拡大できます。
In this instance it is recommended to drag from the centre
この場合にかぎっては中心からドラッグする操作を推奨します。
in order to keep scale properties in proportion.
これはプロパティの拡大を均一に保つためです。
In the main bar of the Scene view you will see two drop-down menus
シーンビューのメインバーには二つのドロップダウンメニューがあります。
that handle how the Scene view is rendered.
これによりシーンビューのレンダリングを制御できます。
You can switch to wireframe
例えばワイヤフレームに切り替えるか
or look at alpha of how your objects are displayed for example.
アルファにして、オブジェクトがどのように描画されるかみることが出来ます。
These are followed by three toggles.
これらの横には 3 つのトグルボタンであります。
The first toggle toggles lighting in the scene
最初のトグルボタンはシーンのライティングを切り替えます。
The second - whether a skybox is rendered or not.
二つめは、スカイボックスがレンダリングされるかを切り替えます。
And the third allows you to preview audio from the game
そして 3 つめによりゲームのオーディオを
from wherever the editor camera is currently located.
現在のエディタ カメラの位置からプレビューしてします。
The editor camera simply refers to the camera
エディタ カメラとは、単に
that you are looking at the Scene view from.
シーンビューでみているカメラのことをいいます。
It is not a camera object in your scene.
シーンの中のカメラオブジェクトではありません。
So for example if I were to move my camera very far
このため、例えばカメラを
away from the sound source and preview the audio again.
音源から遠く移動して、オーディオをプレビューしてみると、
You can hear that it's quieter than it was before.
さきほどよりもかなり音が静かになることが分かるでしょう。
To the right of the panel are the Gizmo menu and search box.
パネルの右側にあるのが Gizmo メニューおよび検索ボックスです。
The Gizmo menu lets you adjust gizmos,
Gizmo メニューにより Gizmo の調整をできるので
the 2D icon shown in the Scene view
シーンビューのあちこちに表示されている 2D アイコンの設定を変更できるので
to help you identify components in the scene.
シーンにおけるコンポーネントの識別が容易になります。
Such as lights, audio sources or cameras.
例としては、ライト、オーディオ ソース、またはカメラです。
These can be adjusted by size
これらのアイコンの大きさを調整したり
and also be toggled between 2D and 3D.
2D および 3D とするか切り替えることが出来ます。
The search field lets you to search for a particular object by searching for its name.
検索フィールドにより特定のオブジェクトをその名前から検索することが出来ます。
And this highlights the object by fading out other objects in your scene.
そしてシーンにおける他のオブジェクトをフェードアウトさせることにより、必要なオブジェクトをハイライトします。
Again, if you are not focused on the actual object that you've found by searching
繰り返しになりますが、特定のオブジェクトにフォーカスをあててなければ
then you can simply use the Focus feature to find it.
フォーカス機能を使用してみつけることが出来ます。
This search also singles out the object in the Hierarchy
この検索は Hierarchy におけるオブジェクトのみ表示にするため、
so by then selecting the object you were looking for
見つけようとするオブジェクトを選択して
and pressing F to focus, or double clicking -
F キーを押下してフォーカスするか、ダブルクリックすれば
you will then be taken to that object.
そのオブジェクトのところまで移動できます。
The final part of the Scene view you should
最後に、シーンビューの中で理解すべきなのは
understand is the View Gizmo itself.
ビュー Gizmo そのものです。
This allows you to switch from Perspective 3D view
これにより 3D Perspective ビューから
to Orthographic cameras from sides, top and bottom.
横からみたOrthographic カメラや上、下からのビューに切替できます。
When dragging to orbit your view in Orthographic view
Orthographic ビューからドラッグによりカメラ回転をする場合、
you will be switching to Isometric view.
Isometric ビューに切り替わります。
You will be notified of this by the term
この状態になっていることは
ISO written underneath the View Gizmo
ビュー Gizmo の下にある Iso という文字列によって確認できます。
but do not confuse this with actual 3D Perspective view
実際の 3D Perspective ビューと混同しないようにご注意ください。
and be aware that you can switch back to Perspective view
また Perspective ビューに切り替える場合は
simply by clicking on the white cube
ビュー Gizmo の中心にある
in the centre of the View Gizmo.
白いキューブをクリックして下さい。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)